crexendo.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**

Crexendo Business Solutions, Inc. (hereafter “Crexendo”) collects basic client information to optimize your support experience. We respect your privacy, and we assure you that we will maintain and use this information responsibly. 

**Browser Data Collection**

For each visitor to Crexendo.com, as well as any sites operated by our subsidiaries and related companies, Crexendo gathers navigational information about where you go on our websites. This information allows us to see which areas are most visited. This helps us improve the quality of visitors' online experiences by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our website (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site). 

Our server does not automatically recognize any private information like your e-mail address. We do collect the e-mail address of those who communicate with us via e-mail. We also aggregate information on what pages visitors access, as well as user specific information on what pages visitors access or visit and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or account registrations. 

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. Information collected is used to improve the content of our WebPages and to customize the content and/or layout of our page for the benefit individual visitors. 

If you provide us with your email address we may contact you for marketing purposes. If at any time you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail, calling or writing, and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our company. Every marketing e-mail we send also allows the recipient to opt-out by clicking a link at the bottom of the email. 

See the privacy policy of each of Crexendo Business Solutions, Inc.’s products or services for a more detailed description of the privacy policy related to that particular product or service. 

**Terms of Use Statement**

You understand and agree that Crexendo, Inc. as well as any sites operated by our subsidiaries and related companies(including but not limited to Crexendo Business Solutions, Inc.) shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, data or other intangible losses (even if the owners of this site have been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from the use or the inability to use the product(s) and or service(s) or any misuse of the product(s) and or service(s) in a manner not in accordance with their intended use. 

See the terms of use of each of Crexendo Business Solutions, Inc.’s products or services for the usage terms related to that particular product or service.
